May 23, the invocation by The Reverend of All-Sate's Pismar Church.
of your authority, guide them to be the leaders for people need.
Help them see humanity and dignity
in those who disagree with Him
into treat all persons no matter how weak or poor
but reverence Your creation deserves
And finally Father renewed him
With a strength Of You're Presence
In The Joyof Helping To Build A Community
Or Thief But Be Human Person
We asked this through Jesus Christ our Lord
Confident in Your Ignis and Love
What do you think is just to the flag
of the United States of America?
And due The Republic for which
your stands One Nation
Under God
In the Visible
With a little liberty
Just as far off
Before public input
I'm just good with personal appearances
That's where they come at
Five
Plain Bliss
Make a motionary proof
Some birth
Hi
So old
High
Parker
Right
Six
minutes from the July 3rd 2023 regular meeting.
Motion to approve?
Second,
second
It's mayor members of Council
These professionals services were incurred for
June 20th
I'll be half of the city focusing on ongoing legal processes including review and recent GRDA
in FERC filings, improper response.
This is again this for last year's fiscal budget because it was occurred June which
has lasts a few years so that 750 thousand budgets we have 3700 dollars an eight dollar
million dollars.
If the 1,700-10 dollar invoice is approved that would leave a remaining balance of 305
thousand two hundred ninety eight billion dollars in this course and like involves
it got to be used up for the right thank you sorry I was late giving
You can't get any middle out when there's questions on number seven
I read it earlier today.
Motion to approve second,
Mark?
Eight Ward-Leasport's agreement
To bank the grant lake for Q23 dash 40 on that escuator
You've related signing and payment authority
The city manager or his days in need
Mr Brown breasted
Good
The first day of the course
And
You know, you have a bank
I came in at 6.9%
Then we had 5.57 million more best
4.94 million per national
Okay, four point eight five
and thank your friends, way to pay me
In 2.7 years per cent
So he's on top
Of that which actually looks
A little different there
So I was looking at this one
There were 94
Between bank and grant lake in first national
How can we stay local with it?
Oh, so that only within being
That close
Well when i go out for a bit of a day
And then you have to pay me
And the next day
How can we stay local with it?
Oh, so that only within being
That close
Well when i go out for a bit of a day
The blinds
We're going to launch the
At here at this city bay
So you know
I'm in your six months now
To Georgia do
Do e have
Within a certain range and this is within the monetary
There's authorization
To pick
If it
That that's
What?
It's a percentage
I don't have an on me at
But its considerable
Its something
On The Order of 10%
It's a significant
We're talking about it in this instance
So for me i appreciate
Back the grant lake and their bid
But
For my our other
Spinnable 94
And stay with local bank
With first national
Since its ninety four dollars and thirty two cents
I feel like
Our previous one is
I think i'll hear a bit of my opinion
That was not going to go with first national
Since its on ninety four dollars
So
And
Okay
But
What about the same way you have been doing
We were just heard here
About the time
You know
To that
Things
So
We make a motion we can
Make the second lowest or
First national
I'll
Make Motion
The week
From first National Bank
Has anybody been notified of
Of
You
Okay
I think they'll appreciate our
Motor Zill
It's nothing personal
But you know we preach
Local
This is one of the yellow
So from now on
We're not going to give this
Thank You keep going
Going away your go and last be the decision
Because if it was like two thousand dollars
Different
That would bring me to the five hundred
That's why for me it was worth keeping the local
For than I have four dollars
But like Brian said there is two thousand and probably different story
The other one that came in
What we can talk about
Yeah
And what's the 10% of
Value at
Okay, yeah so
So
It's a
I think yeah, and
Yeah
And then
We know this
Well
No
So do we
All off on
This
We don't
That's a
Not all of us
For you
What
So what do you guys
Let me
I'll go ahead and second your motion
Bye
Hi
Debt protect contract
See 18-47
Extension for fiscal year 2324
The amount of 78,448
So may or members
This is our annual
Contract that just happens to be up
For renewal
This contract, however with Tetrotech
Is more than it has been in previous years
It does not mean that we have to modify the budget
In any way this amount of still taking into consideration
When
We set a bunch for next year
But all activities
That's coming up
It is important
In this contract for them to complete
The services required
Which are all related
To the principal day of re-licensing
And somewhat
To
I can go through any
Of those activities but as you
You could see out there
There's a lot
With
Protected mitigate enhancement measures
We've got to pull together
And then the summary report for GRA
Studies that we have
To produce a firm
That will be due early this September
So of course there's just no whole live going on
This is kind
Of 45,000
So you had significantly more
But again lot more activity
In-world in
Is it for services already
Render services to me
To the render
It's absolutely possible
They actually said it was really hard
Because they just don't know what is going
You kind of depends on its influence
So again this
Just improving a number not exceeding at
Make emotional improvements
Okay
So,
And engagement letter with all of your
Sojits to conduct the fiscal year
2223 audit
Just letters giving them permission
To do our auditors that would
That's what I thought
In this one
Rates from last year you know, I don't
If talking my head if
This i think
It is just a
I though it sounded close
Yeah
Second
I
Thank you
Hello
Which is written since the post
Staff reports
Trustee community announcements and adjournment
That's the point
Hi